Guide to the The National Intelligencer Newspaper collection, 1804-1844 MS2128
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
National Intelligencer Newspaper collection
1804-1844
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2128
12 Linear Feet
This collection contains issues of the National Intelligencer newspaper. These issues date from 1804-1844. This is not a complete run. The periodicals department at Gelman Library has Intelligencer on microfilm from 1800-1810 and 1813-1869.
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated to Gelman Library in 1967 by the downtown branch of American University. Additional issues have been added through purchasing.
Historical or Biographical Note
The National Intelligencer began as a tri-weekly, first issued on October 31, 1800. It became a daily in 1813, and ceased publication January 10, 1870. It reported and published Congressional debates, and gained a national reputation as one of the leading newspapers in the United States. Two of the men who owned the paper, Joseph Gales (1786-1860) and William Seaton (1785-1866) reported on important debates in Congress and both later served as mayor of Washington, D.C. in the 1820s and 1840s.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains issues of the National Intelligencer newspaper. These issues date from 1804-1844. This is not a complete run. The periodicals department at Gelman Library has Intelligencer on microfilm from 1800-1810 and 1813-1869.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
United States; United States -- History; Washington (D.C.) -- History; Washington (D.C.)
- National Intelligencer, 01/20/1804 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 01/23/1804 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 01/27/1804 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, February-day unknown 1804 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 01/22/1804 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 11/07/1804 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 01/07/1805 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 01/09/1805 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 01/14/1805 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 01/21/1805 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 01/28/1805 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 01/04/1805 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 01/25/1805 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 06/10/1805 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 10/01/1805 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 03/03/1806 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 05/01/1806 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 08/27/1806 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 09/15/1806 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 10/01/1806 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 10/06/1806 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 10/08/1806 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 10/13/1806 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, December-day unknown 1806 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- National Intelligencer, 01/13/1807 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- National Intelligencer, 08/31/1807 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- National Intelligencer, Vol. VII No. 1094 1807 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- National Intelligencer, 10/26/1807 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- National Intelligencer, 10/27/1807 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Intelligencer, 11/11/1807 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- National Intelligencer, 11/13/1807 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- National Intelligencer, 11/23/1807 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- National Intelligencer, 11/25/1807 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1808 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- National Intelligencer, 06/14/1809 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- National Intelligencer, 06/16/1809 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- National Intelligencer, 06/19/1809 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- National Intelligencer, 06/21/1809 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- National Intelligencer, 06/23/1809 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- National Intelligencer, 06/26/1809 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- National Intelligencer, 06/28/1809 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- National Intelligencer, 06/30/1809 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- National Intelligencer, 07/03/1809 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- National Intelligencer, 07/19/1809 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- National Intelligencer, 11/15/1809 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- National Intelligencer, 12/18/1809 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- National Intelligencer, 12/29/1809 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- National Intelligencer, 04/01/1810 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- National Intelligencer, 04/13/1810 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- National Intelligencer, 04/23/1810 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- National Intelligencer, 05/01/1810 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- National Intelligencer, 05/09/1810 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- National Intelligencer, 06/01/1810 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- National Intelligencer, 06/06/1810 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- National Intelligencer, 06/20/1810 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- National Intelligencer, 07/04/1810 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- National Intelligencer, 07/06/1810 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- National Intelligencer, 07/18/1810 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- National Intelligencer, 07/23/1810 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- National Intelligencer, 08/01/1810 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- National Intelligencer, 08/10/1810 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- National Intelligencer, 08/29/1810 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- National Intelligencer, 09/10/1810 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- National Intelligencer, 09/12/1810 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- National Intelligencer, 10/08/1810 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- National Intelligencer, 10/22/1810 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- National Intelligencer, 11/22/1810 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- National Intelligencer, 11/24/1810 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- National Intelligencer, 12/27/1810 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- National Intelligencer, 03/07/1811 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- National Intelligencer, 04/20/1811 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- National Intelligencer, 05/01/1811 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- National Intelligencer, 05/07/1811 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- National Intelligencer, 05/14/1811 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- National Intelligencer, 06/15/1811 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- National Intelligencer, 06/18/1811 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- National Intelligencer, 06/22/1811 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- National Intelligencer, 09/14/1811 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- National Intelligencer, 10/08/1811 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- National Intelligencer, 10/12/1811 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- National Intelligencer, 11/28/1811 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- National Intelligencer, 11/30/1811 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- National Intelligencer, 12/05/1811 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- National Intelligencer, 12/19/1811 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- National Intelligencer, 12/24/1811 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- National Intelligencer, 01/18/1812 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- National Intelligencer, 01/25/1812 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- National Intelligencer, 01/28/1812 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- National Intelligencer, 01/29/1812 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- National Intelligencer, 03/26/1812 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- National Intelligencer, 03/28/1812 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- National Intelligencer, 03/31/1812 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- National Intelligencer, 05/01/1812 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- National Intelligencer, 05/14/1812 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- National Intelligencer, 05/26/1812 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- National Intelligencer, 06/08/1812 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- National Intelligencer, 06/09/1812 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- National Intelligencer, 06/11/1812 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- National Intelligencer, 06/30/1812 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- National Intelligencer, 08/29/1812 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- National Intelligencer, 09/17/1812 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- National Intelligencer, 09/26/1812 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- National Intelligencer, 01/07/1813 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- National Intelligencer, 06/10/1813 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- National Intelligencer, 06/12/1813 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- National Intelligencer, 08/10/1813 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- National Intelligencer, 11/04/1813 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- National Intelligencer, 11/11/1813 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- National Intelligencer, 11/12/1813 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- National Intelligencer, 12/25/1813 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- National Intelligencer, 01/15/1814 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1814 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- National Intelligencer, 01/15/1814 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- National Intelligencer, 01/17/1814 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- National Intelligencer, 03/08/1814 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- National Intelligencer, 03/19/1814 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- National Intelligencer, 04/21/1814 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- National Intelligencer, 04/30/1814 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- National Intelligencer, 04/22/1815 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- National Intelligencer, 05/01/1815 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- National Intelligencer, 06/15/1815 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- National Intelligencer, 06/22/1815 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- National Intelligencer, 06/24/1815 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- National Intelligencer, 06/27/1815 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- National Intelligencer, 06/29/1815 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- National Intelligencer, 07/01/1815 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- National Intelligencer, 07/18/1815 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- National Intelligencer, 07/22/1815 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- National Intelligencer, 07/25/1815 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- National Intelligencer, 08/01/1815 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- National Intelligencer, 08/19/1815 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- National Intelligencer, 08/31/1815 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- National Intelligencer, 09/05/1815 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- National Intelligencer, 11/11/1815 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- National Intelligencer, 01/11/1816 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- National Intelligencer, 01/20/1816 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- National Intelligencer, 01/23/1816 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- National Intelligencer, 01/25/1816 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- National Intelligencer, 01/13/1816 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- National Intelligencer, 03/28/1816 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- National Intelligencer, 03/30/1816 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- National Intelligencer, 04/09/1816 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- National Intelligencer, 05/04/1816 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- National Intelligencer, 06/27/1816 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- National Intelligencer, 07/16/1816 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- National Intelligencer, 08/27/1816 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- National Intelligencer, 08/31/1816 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- National Intelligencer, 09/14/1816 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- National Intelligencer, 09/19/1816 (Box 2, Folder 149)
- National Intelligencer, 10/15/1816 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- National Intelligencer, 11/14/1816 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- National Intelligencer, 11/19/1816 (Box 2, Folder 152)
- National Intelligencer, 12/14/1816 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- National Intelligencer, 12/31/1816 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1817 (Box 2, Folder 155)
- National Intelligencer, 01/07/1817 (Box 2, Folder 156)
- National Intelligencer, Undated 1817 (Box 2, Folder 157)
- National Intelligencer, 01/09/1817 (Box 2, Folder 158)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1817 (Box 2, Folder 159)
- National Intelligencer, 03/08/1817 (Box 2, Folder 160)
- National Intelligencer, 03/22/1817 (Box 2, Folder 161)
- National Intelligencer, 05/01/1817 (Box 2, Folder 162)
- National Intelligencer, 05/08/1817 (Box 2, Folder 163)
- National Intelligencer, 05/17/1817 (Box 2, Folder 164)
- National Intelligencer, 09/11/1817 (Box 2, Folder 165)
- National Intelligencer, 10/01/1817 (Box 2, Folder 166)
- National Intelligencer, 11/08/1817 (Box 2, Folder 167)
- National Intelligencer, 11/01/1817 (Box 2, Folder 168)
- National Intelligencer, 12/01/1817 (Box 2, Folder 169)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1818 (Box 2, Folder 170)
- National Intelligencer, 01/29/1818 (Box 2, Folder 171)
- National Intelligencer, 03/07/1818 (Box 2, Folder 172)
- National Intelligencer, 03/10/1818 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- National Intelligencer, 03/19/1818 (Box 2, Folder 174)
- National Intelligencer, 03/31/1818 (Box 2, Folder 175)
- National Intelligencer, 04/28/1818 (Box 2, Folder 176)
- National Intelligencer, 05/07/1818 (Box 2, Folder 177)
- National Intelligencer, 05/26/1818 (Box 2, Folder 178)
- National Intelligencer, 07/25/1818 (Box 2, Folder 179)
- National Intelligencer, 11/03/1818 (Box 2, Folder 180)
- National Intelligencer, 12/03/1818 (Box 2, Folder 181)
- National Intelligencer, 01/09/1819 (Box 2, Folder 182)
- National Intelligencer, 01/12/1819 (Box 2, Folder 183)
- National Intelligencer, 01/21/1819 (Box 2, Folder 184)
- National Intelligencer, 01/26/1819 (Box 3, Folder 185)
- National Intelligencer, 01/30/1819 (Box 3, Folder 186)
- National Intelligencer, 03/23/1819 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- National Intelligencer, 04/03/1819 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- National Intelligencer, 07/14/1819 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- National Intelligencer, 07/31/1819 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 November 16 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 November 18 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 7 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 9 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 11 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 14 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1819 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1820 (Box 3, Folder 191)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 4 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 6 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 8 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 15 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 01/17/1820 (Box 3, Folder 192)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 18 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 25 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 January 29 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 03/09/1820 (Box 3, Folder 193)
- National Intelligencer, 04/04/1820 (Box 3, Folder 194)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 May 23 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 06/08/1820 (Box 3, Folder 195)
- National Intelligencer, 06/10/1820 (Box 3, Folder 196)
- National Intelligencer, 06/22/1820 (Box 3, Folder 197)
- National Intelligencer, 06/24/1820 (Box 3, Folder 198)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 July 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 July 15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 July 20 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 July 25 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 07/29/1820 (Box 3, Folder 199)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 August 5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 08/16/1820 (Box 3, Folder 200)
- National Intelligencer, 08/23/1820 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 August 30 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 September 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 September 20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 September 27 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 09/30/1820 (Box 3, Folder 201)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 November 4 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 November 11 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 November 21 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 November 25 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 November 28 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 12/05/1820 (Box 3, Folder 203)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 December 16 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 1820 December 28 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- National Intelligencer, 01/25/1821 (Box 3, Folder 204)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 January 27 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 January 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 February 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 February 6 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 February 8 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 February 17 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 March 8 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 03/10/1821 (Box 3, Folder 205)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 March 10 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 March 13 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 March 31 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 04/03/1821 (Box 3, Folder 206)
- National Intelligencer, 04/14/1821 (Box 3, Folder 207)
- National Intelligencer, 04/21/1821 (Box 3, Folder 208)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 May 5 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 May 19 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 May 30 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 June 13 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 July 4 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 July 7 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 07/14/1821 (Box 3, Folder 209)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 July 14 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 July 25 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 July 28 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 8 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 15 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 18 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 22 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 25 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 August 29 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 September 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 September 5 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 September 22 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 09/29/1821 (Box 3, Folder 210)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 September 29 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 6 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 10 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 13 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 17 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 24 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 27 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 October 31 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 11/03/1821 (Box 3, Folder 211)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 3 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 7 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 10 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 15 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 17 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 20 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 22 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 24 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 27 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 November 29 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 12/01/1821 (Box 3, Folder 212)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 12/08/1821 (Box 3, Folder 213)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 12/11/1821 (Box 3, Folder 214)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 13 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 27 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1821 December 29 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 8 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 10 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 17 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 19 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 22 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 24 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 26 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 January 31 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 February 21 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 February 23 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 March 5 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 4 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 6 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 13 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 16 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 18 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 23 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1822 July 4 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1823 January 11 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1823 January 21 (Box 9, Folder 19A)
- National Intelligencer, 1823 April 5 (Box 9, Folder 19B)
  General
  Signed by John Quincy Adams
- National Intelligencer, 1824 February 17 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 February 17 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 February 19 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 February 21 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 03/16/1824 (Box 3, Folder 215)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 March 20 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 March 25 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 June 8 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1824 August 5 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 March 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 March 31 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 April 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 12 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 14 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 19 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 21 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 May 31 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 June 11 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 June 18 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 June 28 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 July 9 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 July 16 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 July 19 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 July 23 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 July 28 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 August 6 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 August 11 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 August 13 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 September 20 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1825 December 20 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 January 7 (Box 11, Folder 5)